This video shows how to get around
Business Central and where to find
information in the
product. The first page you see is
designed for a business manager. It's a
collection of tasks and information that
are important to someone who is running
a business. We have similar pages for
other roles like accountants, production
planners, and sales managers. Under
activities, we have an immediate
overview of our operational KPIs so we
quickly see what's going on in our
business.
There's also fast access to lists that
we'll often use. For example, we can
quickly view our customers vendors,
items, and so on. You can choose to take
a tour on one of these pages, and
Business Central will show you around.
To return to the RO center, we'll choose
the company
name. Similarly, important actions are
readily available. We can create new
documents, process transactions, and
view detailed reports. If we scroll
down, we can see our performance KPIs.
For example, we can flip through a
series of
charts. If we need to do something
beyond our normal daily activities, we
can get to features and lists that
belong to other departments by using the
navigation bar. Alternatively, if we
know the name of the page we want to
open, we can also search for a page or
report.
When you first start with Business
Central, you can take a guided tour.
Business Central will take you through
the first page. You can also explore
other functionalities, watch videos, and
read articles to help you get
[Music]
started. Thanks for watching this
introduction to Business Central. We
hope you're ready to get started.
[Music]